Guide to the Harold Saunders papers, 1976-2014
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
- Tajikistan Dialogue Document, November 13, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Memoranda and Appeals of the Inter-Tajik Dialogue within the Framework of the Dartmouth Conference, 1993 - 1997 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- The Fifth Tajik Dialogue, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #5, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 20)
- Tajikistan Dialogue - Report for January, March 1994 (Box 18, Folder 21)
- The Sixth Tajik Dialogue, March 1 - 4, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #6, April 25, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- The Seventh Tajik Dialogue, May 10 - 12, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #7, May 15, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #8, June 11-14, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #8, August 2, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Reflections on Tajik Dialogue #9, September 1, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- The Eighth Tajik Dialogue, September 21 - 24, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #9, October 21, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Reflections on Tajikistan Dialogue #9, October 26, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Reflections on Tajikistan Dialogue #9, October 26, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- The Tenth Tajik Dialogue, November 29 - December 1, 1994 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #12 Documents, 1994 - 1995 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #1 Document, circa 1995 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Public Administration Training Program for Tajikistan, circa 1995 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents, circa 1995 (Box 19, Folder 16)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 17)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 18)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #10, March 13, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 19)
- Eleventh Tajik Dialogue, March 28, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 20)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #11, April 10, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 21)
- First Thoughts on Follow-up from Tajikistan Dialogue #11, April 21, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 22)
- The 12th Tajik Dialogue, June 19-22, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 23)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #14, December 5, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- Thirteenth Tajik Dialogue, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- Fourteenth Tajik Dialogue, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #13 Documents, 1995 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents - Part 1, 1996 - 1998 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents - Part 2, 1996 - 1998 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Kettering Foundation Memorandum - Self-Evaluation of the Inter-Tajikistani Dialogue, 1996 - 1997 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Sixteenth Tajik Dialogue, May 21 - 23, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #16, June 5, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Seventeenth Tajik Dialogue, October 8 - 10, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #17, October 16, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Resolving Conflict and Building Civil Society, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Documents on Protocol in Tajikistan Documents, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Eighteenth Tajik Dialogue, February 25 - 27, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Memorandum of the 18th Round of the Inter-Tajik Dialogue, February 25 - 27, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Tajik dialogue - Second Day, February 26, March 26, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Tajik dialogue - Third Day, February 27, March 27 1997 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #15, April 9, 1996 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #18, April 21, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- The Tajik Dialogue - Round 19, May 9 - 11, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #19, May 14, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Memorandum on Inter-Tajik Dialogue #20, October 17, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Tajik Twentieth Dialogue, October 27 - 29, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Memorandum of the 20th round of the Inter-Tajik Dialogue, Moscow, October 27-29, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Inter-Tajik Dialogue #20, November 11, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Tajik Twenty-first Dialogue, February 9 -11, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Tajikistan Dialogue #21 - 30, February 12, 1998 - March 11, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Inter-Tajik Dialogue, June 5-7, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Inter-Tajik Dialogue - Twenty-third Round - Moscow, November 13 - 15, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Inter-Tajik Dialogue - Twenty-fourth Round - Moscow, March 12 - 14, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Inter-Tajik Dialogue - Twenty-fifth Round - Moscow, July 1 - 3, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Intertajik Dialogue, October 7 - 8, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- The Tajik Conflict 1992- 1999, Memoranda 1 - 25, with Floppy Disk in Box, December 17, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Working Glossary of People and Places in Tajikistan, circa 2000 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Document, circa 2000 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Tajikistan Conflict Resolution Table of Contents, circa 2000 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Project Summary - Tajikistan Public Voice Project, circa 2000 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents, circa 2000 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Tajikistan Trip Report, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents, 2000 - 2001 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Inter-Tajik Dialogue - Twenty-Seventh Round, March 31 - April 2, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Inter-Tajik Dialogue - Twenty-Ninth Round, December 1-3, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents, 2001, 2006 - 2007 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Issues Forums in Tajikistan, 2001 - 2002 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Intertajik Dialogue - Thirtieth Dialogue, March 9-11, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 23)
- Intertajik Dialogue - Thirty-first Round, July 20-21, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 24)
- Inter-Tajik Dialogue - Thirty-Second Round, October 15-17, 2001 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents - Includes Floppy Disk in Box 39, 2002 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents, 2002 - 2006 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- "Tadzhikistan Dialogue 21 - 23 March 2003, Snegeri, Moscow region, Russia", March 21 - 23, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Inter-Tajik Dialogue, March 21-23, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- 36th Round of the Inter-Tajik Dialogue, Dushanbe, December 6 - 8, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Inter-Tajik Dialogue - Round 36, December 6-8, 2003 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents, 2003 - 2004 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Participants List of Inter-Tajik Dialogue Meeting Dushanbe, September 20 - October 1, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents, 2006 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Tajikistan Dialogue Documents, 2009 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Subseries 2.3: Peace Dialogues - Other, 1986-2014
- Article "...afterthoughts" on Policy Dialogues by David Mathews, Fall 1986 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Documents on International Relationships, 1986, 1987, 2004 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Building a Common Future - The Armenia - Azerbaijan Initiative, October 1994 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Church and Society - Jubilee Time: Peacemaking Conference- Volume 86, Number 3, January, February 1996 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- International Peace Dialogue Documents, 1997 - 2004 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Public Committee for Democratic Processes Documents, 1991 - 2001 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Map of Eastern Europe, circa 2000 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Copies of Dictionary Pages, Highlighting "Dialogue" and Other Words, circa 2000 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Dialogue about Difference by Saunders, circa 2000 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Documents on RCTF Caspian Conference, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Public Committee for Democratic Processes Reports, 2001 - 2002 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Operationalizing Social Capital: A Strategy to Enhance Communities' "Capacity to Concert" by Saunders, 2002 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Nagorno - Karabakh - Searching for a Solution, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Documents on the Geneva Accord, 2003 - 2004 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Three Models of Democratic Deliberation by Noelle McAfee, circa 2004 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Map of Republic of Mountainous Karabakh, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Photos of Saunders, circa 2005 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Political Perspective on Syria Documents, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Documents on Middle East Negotiations, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Arab-American-European Dialogue Documents, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Arab-American-European Dialogue Documents and Correspondence, 2004 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- American-Arab-European Dialogue Group Meeting Documents, March 9-11, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Expanding the Tent: A Seven-Point Plan for Israeli-Palestinian Peace, March 20, 2004 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Iraq after World War II, circa 2005 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Correspondence and Peace-Keeping Information on Iraq, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Email Correspondence on Middle East, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Email Correspondence and Document on Iraq, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- IISD Final Financial Report, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Understanding Islamism Documents, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Documents on Regions and Dialogue, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Dialogue Meeting Documents, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 10)
- Arab-American-European Dialogue Documents, February 4-5, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Arab-American-European Dialogue Group Paper, April 18-20, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Reform Movements in the Arab World by Basil Eastwood and Randa Slim, April 18-20, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Arab-American-European Dialogue Executive Committee Meeting, April 21, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Establishing a Trilateral US-European - Arab Sustained Dialogue for the Purpose of Exploring the Elements of a New Relationship Between the West and the Arab World by Rand Slim, June 2005 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Nagorno - Karabakh: Viewing the Conflict from the Ground, September 14, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Nagorno - Karabakh: A Plan for Peace, October 11, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- "Out of bloodiness, a certain hope" - Article on Iraq from The Economist, October 22, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- IISD Dialogue on Iraq, October 30 - November 1, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Summary of the Iraq Meeting Deliberations, October 30 - November 1, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- IISD Iraq Meeting, October 21 - November 1, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Meeting with Iraqi Sunni Arabs Memorandum, November 3, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Foreign Relations Documents, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Iraq Sustained Dialogue Documents, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Iraq Reconciliation Efforts Documents, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Dialogue Documents, 2006 (Box 24, Folder 26)
- Dialogue Documents, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Arab-American-European Dialogue Documents, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Documents on "Arab World", 2006 - 2007 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Trilateral American-Arab-European Sustained Dialogue, January 3, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- International Institute for Sustained Dialogue Memorandum of Conversation, January 4, 2006 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Launching a Dialogue for National Reconciliation in Iraq by Basil Eastwood, November 2006 - 2008 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Sunni and Shia Documents, circa 2007 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- "Establishing a trilateral US-European-Arab sustained dialogue for the purpose of exploring the elements of a new relationship between the West and Arab world" - Concept Paper by Rand M. Slim, PhD, circa 2007 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Email Correspondence on Iraq, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Conflict Forum on Islam Documents, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Northern Ireland Documents, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Iraq Sustained Dialogue Initiative Documents, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Iraq Sustained Dialogue Initiative Documents, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Email Correspondence on Iraq, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Arab-American-European Dialogue Documents and "Visit to Egypt" CD-ROM, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- United States Institute of Peace - Special Report - "Iraq's New Political Map", January 2007 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- An Unofficial Sustained Dialogue Supporting Official Reconciliation Efforts in Iraq, January 1, 2007 - December 31, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Trip Report - Meetings in Beirut - February 23 - March 2, 2007, March 13, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Email Correspondence on Beirut, March 15, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- The Marmara Declaration - Iraq and Its Neighbors Dialogue, March 23, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- "The Moderate Muslim Brotherhood" by Robert S. Leiken and Steven Brooke, March, April 2007 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- Iraq Sustained Dialogue - An Unofficial Dialogue Supporting Reconciliation in Iraq - Convened by IPALMO and IISD by Basil Eastwood, April 2007 (Box 25, Folder 22)
- Iraq Sustained Dialogue Initiative, April 21 - 23, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 23)
- The Iraq Sustained Dialogue - Beirut, Lebanon Document, April 21 - 23, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Iraq Sustained Dialogue Paper, April 21 - 23, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Email Correspondence - "Debriefing on Beirut" and List of Participants in IISD/IPALMO Iraq Initiative Beirut Meeting, April 27, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Notes from My Meeting with Mr. Al Khaf, September 18, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Email Correspondence - "Draft list and conference call", September 21, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Email Correspondence - "Iraqi Resistance: Kettering", October 8, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Iraq Sustained Dialogue Initiative Documents, November 2007 (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Email Correspondence - "Calls on Syrian Officials", November 2007 (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Email Correspondence - "Follow-up Thought", November 30, 2007 (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Iraq Sustained Dialogue Documents, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Armenia, Azerbaijan, and Nagorno - Karabakh, 2012 (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Documents on Award Given to George Clooney for His Efforts to Stop Genocide in Sudan, 2013 (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Saunders' Notes Arab-American-European Dialogue, circa 2014 (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Transforming Relationships...Sustained Dialogue Institute - Designing Change - Research 2014 - A Strategy for Transformational Change (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Subseries 2.4: Post-Government Career Work, 1982-2014
- Post-1981 Papers, Presentations, Articles, Chapters of Harold H. Saunders - A personal archive of writing and speaking in the years after his government service - Volume 1 - Part 1, 1982 - 1983 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- Post-1981 Papers, Presentations, Articles, Chapters of Harold H. Saunders - A personal archive of writing and speaking in the years after his government service - Volume 1 - Part 2, 1983 - 1984 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- Post-1981 Papers, Presentations, Articles, Chapters of Harold H. Saunders - A personal archive of writing and speaking in the years after his government service - Volume 1 - Part 3, 1984 - 1987 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- Post-1981 Papers, Presentations, Articles, Chapters of Harold H. Saunders - A personal archive of writing and speaking in the years after his government service - Volume 1 - Part 4, 1987 - 1990 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- Post-1981 Papers, Presentations, Articles, Chapters of Harold H. Saunders - A personal archive of writing and speaking in the years after his government service - Volume 2 - Part 1, 1990 - 1991 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- Post-1981 Papers, Presentations, Articles, Chapters of Harold H. Saunders - A personal archive of writing and speaking in the years after his government service - Volume 2 - Part 1, 1992 - 1995 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Post-1981 Papers, Presentations, Articles, Chapters of Harold H. Saunders - A personal archive of writing and speaking in the years after his government service - Volume 2 - Part 2, 1995 -1996 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- Post-1981 Papers, Presentations, Articles, Chapters of Harold H. Saunders - A personal archive of writing and speaking in the years after his government service - Volume 2 - Part 3, 1997 - 2000 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Post-1981 Papers, Presentations, Articles, Chapters of Harold H. Saunders - A personal archive of writing and speaking in the years after his government service - Volume 2 - Part 4, 2000 - 2008 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Presidents' Perspectives on U.S. Interests in the Middle East by Saunders, October 1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Chapter One and Chapter Two of Discussion Draft, August 1984 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Chapter One and Chapter Two of Discussion Draft, August 1984 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Section One - Presidents and Policy, Discussion Drafts by Saunders, August 1984 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Working Draft of "When Walls Come Down" - Part 1, circa 1986 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Working Draft of "When Walls Come Down" - Part 2, circa 1986 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Working Draft of "When Walls Come Down" - Part 3, circa 1986 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Preface Material for Manuscript, circa 1986 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- Chapter 1 - The Real Middle East Problem, circa 1986 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Unfinished Manuscript - "New Directions in Foreign Relations - The United States in the Changing Middle East", 1986 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- Foreign Policy Discussion Document and Notes, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Doc 1 Master, September 29, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Doc 2 Master, September 29, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Doc 4 Master, September 29, 1986 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- Manuscript Pages - Part 1, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- Manuscript Pages - Part 2, 1987 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- The Concept of Relationship by Saunders, April 14, 1989 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- Manuscript Pages, circa 1990 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- The Politics of International Relationships by Saunders, circa 1990 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- Officials and Citizens in International Relationships - The Dartmouth Conference by Saunders, circa 1990 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- Annotated Manuscript Pages, circa 1990 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- Sinai II: The Politics of International Mediation by Cecilia Albin, May 24, 1990 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- "Thinking in Stages" Manuscript - Part 1, June 1991 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- "Thinking in Stages" Manuscript - Part 2, June 1991 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- Assistant Secretary Dr. Harold Saunders - Oral History Transcript of the Foreign Affairs Oral History Program (Georgetown University) Interviewed 1993 - 94, 1993 - 1994 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Note from Saunders on Later Career, circa 2014 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Series 3: Notebooks, Media, and Miscellaneous (Boxes 30 - 40), 1970s-2000
  This series includes multiple notebooks and recordings on cassette tape on experiences during and after Saunders' career in government.
  - Four Perspectives on Ethics and Foreign Policy and Their Implications for Some Central Issues of Current U.S. Policy by Kenneth W. Thompson, July 1977 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Moral Reasoning and Foreign Policy, with Special Emphasis on Human Rights, August 29, 19773 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - United States/Middle East Diplomatic Relations 1784 - 1978 - An Annotated Bibliography by Thomas A. Bryson, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Foreign Policy and Morality - Framework for a Moral Audit, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Foreign Policy and Ethics Documents, circa 1980 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - The Politics of International Relationships by Saunders, circa 1980 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Documents on Foreign Policy, circa 1980 (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Documents on Foreign Policy Ethics and Morals, 1985 - 1987 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Documents on Nixon's Policies, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Richard Nixon's Reactive Approach to Middle East Policy by Steven B. Hedlund (Saunders' intern), March 1, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Intervention: Normative Foundations, Political Meaning and Policy Choices by J. Bryan Hehir, October 23, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Nuclear Ethics, Joseph S. Nye, Jr., 1988 (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Documents on Jewish-Arab Relationship, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - "An Ethical Basis for a Theory of International Relationship", 1988 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Ethics and International Relations, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Memorandum on Ethics of Negotiation, April 14, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Documents on Political Settlement in Persian Gulf, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Documents on Carter Administration and Camp David Accords Conference, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Beyond Government - Extending the Public Policy Debate in Emerging Democracies, 1995 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Toni Morrison Princeton Convocation Address from Princeton Alumni Weekly, November 27, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Contemporary concerns Grosvenor Books - Creative answers, 1997 - 1998 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Origins - NC Documentary Service, Volume 17, No. 28, March 3, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - The Carter Presidential Center Booklet, circa 2000 (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Pre-Camp David Notebooks, circa 1980s - 1990s (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Pre-Camp David Notebooks, circa 1980s - 1990s (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Pre-Camp David Notebooks, circa 1980s - 1990s (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Pre-Camp David Notebooks, circa 1980s - 1990s (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Pre-Camp David Notebooks, circa 1980s - 1990s (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Presidential Policymaking Tapes, circa 1980s (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Notebooks - Final Week of Iranian Hostage Crisis, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous AV Materials, circa 1980s - 1990s (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Certificates, Awards, and Photos of Diplomatic Functions, circa 1980s (Box 40, Folder 1)